<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>docker on Josh Butts | joshbutts.com</title>
    <link>https://joshbutts.com/tags/docker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in docker on Josh Butts | joshbutts.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://joshbutts.com/tags/docker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Patching Xdebug performance issues on Docker for Mac</title>
      <link>https://joshbutts.com/posts/patching-xdebug-docker-for-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joshbutts.com/posts/patching-xdebug-docker-for-mac/</guid>
      <description>Background on how Docker for Mac works Docker is a Linux-only technology. Docker for Mac uses a small (very small) Linux VM to implement what &amp;ldquo;feels like&amp;rdquo; native Docker support on Mac OS. The VM is implemented using XHyve and MacOS&amp;rsquo;s not-much-publicized native hypervisor support. The fact that Docker runs in a VM is ultimately the source of this issue, though that&amp;rsquo;s not being entirely fair.
Why is everything that has to do with time in computing hard?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced TablePlus usage from the command line on MacOS</title>
      <link>https://joshbutts.com/posts/tableplus-shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joshbutts.com/posts/tableplus-shortcuts/</guid>
      <description>Foreword I spent probably about half of my professional career as a hardcore Navicat user. Navicat was an actual good SQL GUI (MySQL specifically) that worked on Windows. When I later moved to MacOS, they had a version there too, though it never really felt as polished as the Windows version. Navicat still exists, but for whatever reason I transitioned to Sequel Pro (&amp;ldquo;Pancakes&amp;rdquo;). I used that for many years, but alas, it has become somewhat abandonware.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Traefik, Docker, and Let&#39;s Encrypt to manage multiple local development projects</title>
      <link>https://joshbutts.com/posts/traefik-docker-local-dev/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joshbutts.com/posts/traefik-docker-local-dev/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR Fine, just skip directly to the Github repo that has a complete example of how to do this:
https://github.com/jimbojsb/traefik-docker-local-dev
My expectation is you make your own private version of this repo with these files as the skeleton. You may never need anything more than these files depending on how crazy you want to get with the feature set of Traefik.
Background This is something multiple people have asked me how to achieve, so I finally sat down to write this up.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>